Eralp ÖZCAN

Full Stack Developer | Frontend Developer

• eralpozcan eralpozcan istanbul

I'm currently a Full Stack Developer. I have been developing myself in the field of Frontend, Backend since 2021. Previously, I had an adventure in artificial intelligence and data analysis for 2 years. I enjoy working in the software field as I have transitioned from the automation field. Since I have the opportunity to work in many interdisciplinary fields, I can easily adapt. In my spare time, I like reading, playing the piano, traveling and exploring new places.

Professional Experience

Floressional Experience	
 Frontend Developer, TatilDükkkanı I'm developing on the Tatildukkani project with Vue.js/Nuxt2. I'm developing on Passenger Travel with AngularJS. 	06/2024 – present İstanbul, Turkey
 Frontend Developer, Protein Tech I worked as a developer on an inventory tracking/cost management and POS application called Simpra Inventory and Simpra POS with Vue.js. I'm in an agile (scrum) team thus well familiar with the methodology, principals and rules. Working with industry standard tools such as Jira, Swagger, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Postman, ESLint, SonarQube; and actively implementing outputs from Figma. 	10/2022 – 06/2024 Istanbul, Turkey
Full Stock Douglanay Arms Croup Holding	09/2022 10/2022

Full Stack Developer, Arma Group Holding

08/2022 – 10/2022 Development of projects Vue3 and Node.js(Fastify) Gebze, Kocaeli, Turkey

- Software development for Ads-Advertise platform
- Software development Drive platform
- Development of with Sequelize ORM and PostgreSQL

Freelancer, Upwork 08/2021 - 10/2022

- Development of projects with HTML CSS and JS, Vue
- Software development for gaming platform with Lua and SQL.
- Data Analysis and Visualization

Education

Mechatronics Engineering, Karabuk University	2013 – 2019
 Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning Laboratory. I have been in various 	Turkey
studies. This ResistorNet-DirencNet academic poster.	
 I have gained experience and knowledge about autonomous systems, 	
automation systems and mechatronics systems.	
Business Administration and Management, Anadolu University	2017 – 2023
Cost, Organization Development and Entrepreneurship.	Turkey

Skills

Vue.js • Vuex • Vuetify • Nuxt3	Node.js RestAPI MongoDB Postgresql	Front-end • HTML • SCSS • Javacript
PiniaOrganizations	• Docker	 Tailwind
 Kodluyoruz, Master Assistant Master Assistant Mentor Bootcamp Acceleration Mer Protein Full Stack Bootcamp 	ntor	06/2021 – 09/202 Turke
	tifi, AI Researcher at Deep Learnin earch and Development Platform	-
World Food Programme, Boo • React.js Bootcamp with the • Flutter Bootcamp with the k	Kodluyoruz	06/2022 – 09/202
-	_	12/2017 – 06/202 2019)
Projects		
Commite, Project FounderOpen Source Social Media FVue.js,Node.js,Socket.io	or Developers	06/2022 – preser
Reinforcement Learning Wor • Multi-armed bandits works	-	07/2018 – 07/201
ResistorNet-DirencNet, Rese • Creation of resistance data a • I did the research and devel • We created the data with D • Dataset is in Kaggle.	and classification by Deep Learnin opment part of the project.	05/2018 – 06/201 ng.
Publications		
ResistorNet-DirencNet, IDSE	W'18	06/201

- Creation of resistance data and classification by Deep Learning.
- I did the research and development part of the project.
- We created the data with Deep Learning Lab. members.
- Dataset is in Kaggle.

Languages

English Hungarian В1 Α1